Xavion, how are you? How you doing? I'm
doing good. Good, good. Hey, did I read
are you related to Walter Payton and if
so, how?
Someone somewhere down along them lines.
It's still a long way. I ain't going to
lie.
Did you did you hear stories about him
growing up or or how do you how do you
know all this? Yes, so my grandfather
just walked by me like 5 minutes ago
and was just telling me another story
about how they slept in the same bed and
stuff like that.
But landing at the Bears, you know, the
place that made him famous,
what does that mean to you?
It mean a lot. Just the opportunity to
be able to to to to play
at the highest level the highest. I'm
just blessed.
What do you know about the Bears and
Caleb Williams and all that sort of
stuff?
Yeah, I was I had a long conversation
about 2 weeks ago
with the staff and I was telling them
like Caleb Williams remind me of Aaron
Rodgers a lot. So I'm familiar with
them. I would watch his tape, see what
he could do and see what he can pull off
and the sky's the limit. Did you come up
here for that?
Say it again. Did you Did you talk to
them on a visit up here or or No, sir.
No, sir. It was a phone call. Phone
call. Okay. Thank you. Sir.
Dan.
Hey Xavion, congratulations.
I appreciate you. I appreciate you. You
bet. How do you describe your game as a
receiver overall?
Versatile. I'm able to do everything.
It's not none that I can't do. I can go
on the outside and play, go to slot, go
to running back and make plays. So
versatile for sure. How much do you know
at this point about Ben Johnson's
offensive creativity and and what maybe
he might envision for you?
Yes, sir. I I seen them putting up a lot
of points last year, so I'm I'm going to
get to know everything about them in a
couple of weeks.
You're also described as a fearless
returner.
What do you remember about the the
return against Vanderbilt?
Yes, sir. I just I was just told by my
receiver coach.
Actually the drive before that like we
had went down two scores away and he was
explaining it to me like
this one big play is make big plays. So
I know whenever the opportunity came, I
had to make a big play no matter how it
came to me.
John.
Hey Xavion, congrats. Did I hear
somewhere that you threw a couple of
passes last year, too? Yes, sir. I threw
a couple I did everything last year. It
ain't nothing that you can name that I
ain't do. What what does that just say
about your versatility?
Athlete. Like I said, it ain't nothing
that I can do. I kind of left throwing
the ball out there, too, but they always
ask just from a receiver standpoint, but
like I said, like I'm able to do
everything.
Courtney.
Xavion, what was your goal for the
combine, the time that you wanted to
run?
That was my goal the whole entire time.
I was I was telling everybody, my peers,
my family, everybody like I'm about to
go out there and run a 4 2. I don't know
what it's going to be. I don't know if
it's going to be a 4 2 1 or a 4 2 9, but
I know it was going to be it was going
to be somewhere along those lines. I
know what I prayed for.
I know what I talked to God about. I
know what I manifested. So when I did
it, it didn't really surprise me. It was
more like I told you so to everybody
else.
Dan.
Yeah, Xavion, I was just going to ask
you what your initial reaction was when
when that that 40 was over. That's
That's exactly what it was. Actually,
while I was running it, I had took like
a bad step in the way while I was
running it. So immediately in my in my
mind, cuz you know when you run a 4 2,
everything kind of got to be perfect. So
when I took the bad step in my mind, I'm
like, dang, I just ran a 4 3. But after
after the fact, I was coming back. I
heard the crowd get a little loud and it
was like
a man that was that was working for the
staff for the combine. He had like made
a face at me
like what I ran. He said 4 2 8. I was
like, yeah.
I knew it was coming.
Xavion, the Bears have said that they're
they're looking for competitors and guys
that bring a a certain level of energy.
Feels like you've got kind of a natural
energy. How do you describe that for the
folks in Chicago of what of what you
bring to the table in that regard? Yes,
sir. It's It's been something that I've
been having in me since I was a kid
since I fell in love with the game. I
just I play the game with a different
type of aggression with a different type
of mentality cuz at the end of the day
this
It's my job.
It's my life. This is what I do. So I
put everything in me in this game of
football.
Last question, Sean.
Xavion, when you're a return man, you're
kind of on an island out there. Can you
just describe for us what your mentality
is as as you're sitting back there
waiting for the football?
Yes, sir. So when I'm when I'm at punt
return, first of all, my main focus is
not giving the ball back, not putting
the defense in a compromised position.
So first you got to secure the ball.
Then after that, get the first first get
the first first down for the offense and
and and if it goes off the races after
that, then come dance with me in the end
zone. But
as far as kick return,
I go out there and I just
That's That's one cut. You got one cut
there in kick return. You see that hole,
you make one cut and you got to make one
man missing. Like I said, me in the end
zone.
Last one, Dan.
All right, Xavion. What what is the
celebration tonight? What was the
reaction when you when you finally got
the call?
I can't even explain that feeling.
That's That's a feeling I I I never I
never had before. Um
First of all, I just like giving all the
glory to God. Without him, I I wouldn't
be in this position. So
I'm just blessed to have my family
behind me.
All my loved ones who watched me
throughout this whole entire journey.
Like I said, it like it was just a
feeling that that I never felt before.
It's kind of crazy like I was actually
I walked out the house to go grab some
Vaseline in my car.
And
as soon as I came from by the car,
I heard my phone ringing. I looked at
the phone.
I was just like, dang, like it's it's
happening.